the winner of the corporate social
responsibility award goes to
prudential vietnam
congratulations to prudential vietnam
let's welcome the representative from
prudential vietnam to the stage to
receive this award
miss julian von on
director of corporate social
responsibility from prudential vietnam
assurance
ladies and gentlemen uh thank you very
much um it is our great honors to be
here tonight on behalf of prudential
vietnam to get these awards
um
this is
absolutely
a meaningful gift
for us uh since this year we celebrated
the 15-year anniversary of prudential
vietnam since the first day we
we we set our footprints in vietnam
market
absolutely for the first 15 years
we have been committed to the csr
of
to bring the betterment for vietnamese
people
we've done we've done a lot of things
for for thousands of vietnamese people
and children um to to have a better life
and this become a part of our core
values for 2 000 staff and 110 000
agents of prudential vietnam
so thank you so much thank you thank you
miss on
and thank you mr oj sakova for
presenting this award for us